Moon.
Early it failed.
And failed.
A rats what was.
The. Man and.
The man and.
A was not more first isolated
from the outside world
by walls of granite.
But so you could get out of it by merely
telling what you know. You may lay not
being of the scope of the old bloke. But
I will give you the same laws like any
other. Still has two years
eight bunches six days left
in which to make music
a book. That will be sold at auction for
the benefit of this to let postings for.
Ten just for
a. Moment
on. And now we go with the next subject on
our list for I can't say objects because
there are three of them now ladies and
gentlemen he's going to be brought together
all separately. He has been one of the
musical boxes only arrived this morning and
I didn't intend to put them on the Op
You're going to like that I'm going to tell
them it was all good friends is not all bad
I'm not going to leave society and then
be your Ts. And what do you. Write. The
beautiful thing to think of the music
about. What a lovely thing is what
a Beautiful Gift created
on made by loving and
a thing of the day and you can
always at the top. It's about upon.
The Do the end. Is
a comma so in the house
we go to the. One about.
Ten shillings. Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen
tentative up a broom is
a go box it wouldn't buy anywhere in London
for less than the five. Of us didn't
give it a go but then shillings
like they can milk from
a baby or I was going to get into
the dental essentials of attention
a little bit into the but then what of
the one pound where we want our one time
love to be
a pound. One pound another one pound another
ladies and gentlemen the numbers are
going to get you know to two hundred two
pounds. Don't power still pound it up but
to Bundaberg I want my turn I have called.
The old of the gentleman but all powers
. Suddenly idea. Now ladies and gentlemen
comes the opportunity to purchase an
exact duplicate of the because of the
little musical box just bought by this
gentleman for the ridiculous low price of
two that I deducted same sex is I made of
the same and you know that lovely I think
you think you think you think you sound
like bubbles to me you know the
labels pulling on the rope
a little bit about who stuck with you found
out about it out of the truth about.
Who will do the other we might all this
stuff for the London please buy for me get
two pounds from
a not nor my degree in Scotland decide I
don't like these men one pound ten to one
about one pound one pound one thousand up
with one pound it up by one pound pound
but once I'm quite certain
a lot smaller. Than they did run
down. But giving my idea thank you
if we can get the photo out of these good
little musical boxes that the same thing
to think that lovely. Ladies and
gentlemen I don't really get
a galley in this window because this is the
exact replica of those two are just so
grateful.
When closed but this is extraordinary
important. Come into coming
times college or just but I don't want
fortunate came to late arriving in time to
bid on certain articles which I was rather
anxious to take perhaps. We all carry
several things over. What my the articles
these three identical musical boxes about
. I'm sorry so but they are so if you weren't
here to bid on them they didn't bring
anything like the real value thanks just
to obtain them I want to kill records with
children who the purchases when we don't
usually give out that information to
protect shall we say sentimental reasons I
am most anxious to get in touch with the
purchases I've been waiting
to pay. When for certain
sentimental reasons so would then have to
realize how credit did I say three years
ago Buffett was about. The first purchase
for two pounds Mr Julian every fifty to
risk their right to dress down have. Certainly
been in a long I'm fortunate my D.H.
Is
a dealer you see they don't like is the No
the thing that on account of the profits
. The purchase it was a
woman can you give me
a description often I would fully Toller
send the. Light complexioned and out
here. And she was wearing a gray
suit dental member she probably runs
a good shop she paid one pound
you say she comes here fairly
frequently telling didn't say so but she
got. Like is not you coming on Thursday we
have sales on Mondays and Thursdays. And
the banks. And the do we make you know
one forty three do you have to
weigh the ten shilling quite
a drop from two pounds this to can go was
a Scotchman. Thank you
that's helpful. Thank you
and it's done yes I think we all would
have LOVED IT things to say oh God just
thank you. Back to the.
Message reached just too late.
To call boxes the beams.
Let's get out of here.
Someday you'll go to. Reaching for us.
To whom
a touch of. This interview and. The
Musical Box of their dreams go on
a date if you my dad isn't my fault that
the message reaches only an hour ago. My
fault that they were so. Content never
sponsible for that. Book for your sake.
Well upon you tonight for the quote of doing
to jump to the need to consult you'll
find that out of the very deepest moment.
Member that I. Know two years ago.
That. He had left the striking of
the movement was the response I had
a. Lot of mine.
But nothing but enough to. The great shallow
comes in so I think the new issue of
The Strand magazine is out containing and
out of the OSs like to do it to. What you
call this one I call it.
A title that. If you
must be called my ex but I do wish
you'd put less emphasis on that
a dramatic vote on the intellectual issues
involved. What you mean by that when I
do hope you've given. The woman so if
you had been you know by the woman
I suppose you mean I mean had
is will always remember.
As the woman.
In fact there are very ally our I although
I haven't seen you for years I want you
to meet my friend shall go down this is
stinking In other words you never read
one has often spoken of you. Yes we were
in school together it's more years ago and
I can remember but you didn't come any I
just remind me that you know I just happen
to be in the neighborhood and saw your
lights burning so I took the liberty of that
you are still writing your
history stuff here is
a new one out this week got out of this is
a good thing I said that Ben It makes you
look very interesting still poking your
nose into other people's business as usual
which you haven't devalues the reason
suddenly not being on the head of my own
living will then proceeded to commit them
a C.D.R.
To where you ever heard up so that
must mean by me as it could. If
you like
a cup of tea or. Are going to listen. When
you said the robbery was idiotic the
tremor oversimplified the fact that it was
about five thousand pounds out of his
school buses in my living will the people I
quote in the act. Was
passed out I gather you are
a collector of musical boxes Yes I have
read some of the very beautiful but not the
one of the Stella that he evidently grabbed
the first thing that came to his hand
when the had me coming into the room
which is rather odd isn't it that having
disposed to be on you didn't pick up something
more than double. Was there anything
unusual about Starbucks. So I picked
up enough avocados several years
ago you see you have many valuable music
boxes yet to teach made up of one that
isn't worth five pounds sounds like rather
an intriguing little problem read I take
it you're just an ordinary petty
thief didn't know the value that is
a possible explanation and yet I venture
to say that the average petty thief has
a more extensive knowledge of the very
rough Jadar than the average collector. In
a way that govern the odds that they
didn't get very excited about it that's
consistent anyway. I wonder about my tio
collection Mr Emery constant that has
nothing to connect the legs more than
showing how he's planted evidence that you
cannot present good by place it
does sound important but yes right.
So I'll. Take it as an attitude oh I'm
sorry they're going around to my place but
I'm going to give you something better
than tea. Now this autumn as they deliver
the fifteenth and is one of the better
if you were still in existence in that
period and the particular finds that's
a. Challenge. Quite.
Sounds a little like a lot of mice
running about a ten room. No it's
a musical I mean good old band
playing around you Mark you have
a little cynical tweet tweet.
It is.
Stupid to see. The Because we have had is
a very bad right bad just read about it
there and about think we're bringing back
bad of six hundred pounds
a day with the General Franks election
the crew still has an idea like
a musical box passes up one of the five
hundred pounds for one of us nobody was
a total moron. And. Others are still
about Jack mystery or just plain
wooden box about. As matter fact I have
read over here almost exactly like if. I
picked it up you have to be at an auction
room in MacSpeech to get me to browse but
I wouldn't live on
e Bay ad when I get to my collection
but. I never heard of. The
the.
You have a remarkable ear for
music hence the NEWSROOM in
a day if you download bank. You think
about that box of options out there
yes
a lot of action rhythms in magic rich run
by I don't know what to name Crabtree.
But out of the rubble committed. To tax
money you know none of them are in that box
and the robbery might well be cause and
effect especially since you said that this
doesn't box I put it resembles this one
a great deal and it's got some yard
but not particularly interested
a year so that I wouldn't stand for that
especially as I told him I had quite an
able to describe the feel except
across that affected it was definitely
a man probably remembers it again some.
Struck him on the head pass next thing I
know and then
a stranger about me back to rise you put
that box away from I look it up I don't
think that night so he said everything's
in general I'd rather pleased to manage
that attempted robbery I made I'd suggest
that you call the police and I have been
running into personal danger rather
doing a bit of an elaborate than not
a message don't stink it
seems to me rather you have
a mountain out of the mask you are not
a village to read or write it's time
you were in bed things are not adding
a sea of red as if you can get me to go.
Like not understand why no service to
this seems to me that I didn't heed explanation
was an example that really Scotty I
don't believe it was anything else I didn't
family did to be anything other than
P.C. It is very obvious when
I got you however it's often
a mistake to accept something as true
because it's obvious. The truth about me
arrived at by the painstaking process
of eliminating the Andrew. B.
I'm not able to do that in this case not
for the data but rather here pulling my
leg created trying to turn to the tech never
rabbit into an international practice
not just separate your friends think you
know the stuff in the future just in case
.
This. Is.
Their. Job and I may get
a little. That occurs out of
everything of this is cut. If
you ever run back Spraberry aborting the
data for then chances are. That that's
just until
a six hour ad. They gave their dreams.
It's interesting come straight up now to
the door at night. That
as well. As for the
counting the trial. Now I mean. That.
He's doesn't have the ballot. In the pixy
and. I know it's in the corridor so late
but I know the particular to around the
corner and I'm going to take him to see
a collection of musical boxes the idea of
this go at me for years all the greater
for being so unexpected my friend called
me you know that. One called me think you
think you have quite
a perfectly wonderful collection of musical
back to you now you tell me you had
a collection I had no idea it was our
turn. To the beer as well as to the.
Oh what a feeling this
one was this just like
a country cousin amid all this gratitude
and I don't know how you have
underestimated the country
gotten out of it out of there is
a bit of it yes it was all these to some
one thousand one bit of us trying to say I
don't mind that that's the box of us but
I do resent this trick on the scope that
it makes you look so interesting
because using. That it's
a little sad says it best though I mean the
Dr Watson he was here this evening with
him. He's interested in my collection to
Sherlock Holmes Yes you know him I've
heard of him. He seems to think I'm
in some sort of the danger but
a haunting tune it takes me right back to
my childhood isn't it odd that you should
be it's fitting that particular interest
about why because Mr Holmes is also into.
Isn't it you may have been more interested
in the tuna in the box idea just as I
remember now because of that note to
note having heard only one their way in
a few remarkable men. It is
a bizarre miss to be largely Don't you
believe in wanting God that would want
a book like that I would not.
But I am. If you can put me
at a very awkward position I'm
a collector you know that and the collector
values but never sell but if the price
was high on
a. Price and I don't do it
it's the principle. Yes
Well we haven't had that drink now
thanks I must be getting along. A Syrian
and bread. End up working out
on the other you my reputation
I think. You know you have
a protective thing. You
told me to wait outside you have to kill
before. I had to walk out with this the
hell you any guys don't touch
him to. Get out I'm sorry.
This is not. About Scotland Yard
but about Sherlock Holmes. Now.
Did you get it. Good. Did you have any
trouble with it just
a matter of nada. About Mr Holmes
Poppins thanks for coming so prompt
a second the thought suggested that
I called to tell you Mr Emery was
a client of Mr Holmes that maybe I didn't
mention that when I telephoned you Mr
Holmes Well not exactly exactly Specter
Sergeant Thompson he was killed between the
hours of eleven and two o'clock this
morning Mr Holmes that's been so many knew
someone of whom we had no suspicion. Who
stink you so my fault I should have
prevented this and I was not under start
talking about that not out. Of bounds it's
gone. That's the second attempt on the
musical box that I bought the auction sale
and this time it was successful
says I was two pounds that was
a man's life what I think we better to have
is it again not auction and that's what
Crabtree inspect and I suggest that you
make a complete set of this flat for
a small plane musical box about
that size thank you and I want to
say the first box when you get to do an M.
Or a second to kill go one forty three B.
Hampton away the third to the unidentified
young lady who presumably has
a shop and lives there go to
agree that right Mr Holmes is
a rather strange Mr Crabtree that you have
had three identical musical boxes all
playing the same tune with a come from
God more Persian does not really get
a regular shipment from there every month
the image manufactured the way to make
all kinds of things pop racks wastepaper
basket musical but did you happen to
notice if anyone tried any particular
interest during the auction and the
purchasers of these three boxes are going
to Crabtree this is better literally
a matter of life and death and you
put it that way Mr Holmes was
a gentleman came in at about an
hour after telling one an illusion
a state he was in it five times ten with
a box and on Twitter then the sentimental
value point to it splits of sentiment can
you describe him taller distinguished
looking man had they had
a mustache who is quite
a gentleman to what was his reaction when
you were unable to supply him with the
address of the young lady on the shop I
told him the young lady usually come back
on Thursday he said he'd come back on days
you know that's the part that you meant
to get three You've been very helpful thank
you I don't know about them. But I'm
going to still go. Talk.
Hang it all home how do you know those other
two musical boxes are then important I
don't but I said I have no intention
of waiting till the owner is
a method to find out. What to
do. I hope that explanation
I'll have
a look through this window. This
is Jim did anyone love.
Still play seems like was
a. Yes this misses care about them but now
when you expect them now when an average
down there's no use your in
a bath they don't buy nothing from pencils
and those good move them into shallow
Combs aka who want your money to come in
and wait that business is right I don't
know I have got to go out to do my shopping
and I don't know if this is like any
strangers know it's been about quite alright
I feel you know I've got to pay off
like an apology and not deny that
this is good luck with the house.
But I'll get out of it.
But.
It's not playing hockey right now what
with the likes of you be doing in PA blind
now don't worry about the fifth step
you navigate the problem now but.
You know how much I've been thinking that's
been something hidden in that box most
ink is so did you notice
that. Lots of homes this is.
Which is just even the water parks.
Wow the. Cock. Got to have
it on the chin. All right.
It's all of that. You don't cut him are you
telling me you have to stare at me and
I know I know she won't come back just
to show how your new musical bugs.
Sister Why do you. Think. You know I'm
not I don't want to nobody nobody
when your music about here is about in the
best one in London what you. Will want
to prove up what you mean and she took the
musical box out issues in that market
basket right to about that he knows he's
right to duty to God child women want to
take the music box she isn't to kill the
child woman to the consummate actress
extreme because I'm scrupulous
woman it was topic nothing to get
a fertile it was And tonight tonight
parents get back saying everything to them
close to one of but homes where you going
somewhere somehow I must get to the young
lady of about that musical box before on
opponents find out I only hope that I
won't be too late.
You must abide in my chair up with you
tonight to hell uncle I can I said
that.
Now it isn't just about how
much I offer but this gives
a brew lazed China I think you read. The
French call now this is the genuine
article What does it differ on about the
amount of peas all you could use it
doesn't that these on the dining room
table now is some of the stuff with
a ten pound somebody stuck with
a ten pounds. Alright five I
found another five pounds of
a five pounds up and I found Stan five
pounds fifteen five. Six pounds over six
pounds six pounds going once going twice
and I was going to be all down so it was
a different six pounds next we have
a real museum for us ladies and gentlemen
a fine nineteenth century. Costume
an exact replica. Peasant women.
Gentleman not of like fifteen to twenty
pounds which can jump. Like that when
two pounds forty two pounds two
pounds two pounds brown. One
pound anybody any one pound one. I'm
not going to waste your valuable
time or mine in trying to get one of what
this good. The only Beaconsfield for one
pound that child support was going once
going twice at the last quarter and it was
sold to the young lady for one about.
Now if you don't want my eyes grow your
attention to something which may be right
surprised you well the only collection
The only other one like it in the British
Museum is I mean bolts of the civil
Dynasty this board lay in
a large collection somewhere outside Rome
for over two centuries I understand it
was discovered there by the noted on the
clearance and republished some of you may
remember and recalled with besides being
a noted Governor as it clearly is also
a gentleman right to go in the post
and. You show that the GO she picks up
and then the auction is description
follow Jaime.
It's the D.M.
And only one pound he can get at least
three find it easy I'll go make some tea I
could do with
a copyright. Good afternoon good
afternoon I'm looking for the day gift for
a seven year old girl what would you suggest
we have many don't know about this I'm
getting I think she has enough dolls
already books are always welcome Well I'm
looking for something in
a different that's probably true
to whether this well that's
a musical box children always not something
that is an exception and I plan. Many
feuds.
Have you any others yes you guessed
it the way I have only to this.
It is going to give us some
phone without a hard to find
a prime time unless. I get to
point out that some didn't have
a Sawston but it was on its own and wouldn't
run it would do the nice gift thing
and then. Do you happen to know
a little purchase it was play yes he left
his card just in case anyone to Clapham.
How interesting. I'm sorry but I'm
afraid I'll have to look at the thank
you anyway. About No thank you.
But I can now run one job up in.
A box I might have known. We were
hunters. On the bridge maybe
I'm too good full of it played right
into his hand. Of Cards. Because it's
followed God luck. So many
front of the Taj shot.
How many ten shots brought to the
next corner and again at the next.
Now photographs of a commission
that nobody expected is not
a non-criminal without expecting those
who do find that she was disguised as
a child to go running off I. Never see it
again I recognize. It Or going on to we
know who they are and where they are but
who's covering them that such an Times and
find them get away from him is a
good man he could have arrested them
a to try shop we had no proof but we know
that they killed them or at proof might
happen we must have proof. We have X.
Rated so there's nothing whatever
conceal in the box we have the tapes.
Must be some through and it's probably so
obvious that we've all of it up it seems
to me what up against
a bunch of lunatics not going to fix my dad
but I'll still be asked to come but it
matters what can these little musical boxes
having them so important don't forget
they were made in Dakar prison he smuggled
stuff into prison not out you want to
break the box apart to see
if there's anything the X.
Ray hadn't caught No not yet
and about to get Thanks.
The government of Dakar prison and from
that not that I missed out on the question
that all three musical boxes were made by
the same company John David seven at that
Mia tense that David Bank of England played
better be off and. Now we're getting
somewhere if we can and how
did you know about. I'm
a student of crime inspector that I make
my business to know about that thing when
the name of Davidson is mentioned who is
this for the day that as long as Mr Holmes
seems to know all about it already I suppose
there's no harm in telling you. I told
you the goal in London that
occurred a robbery at such
a command disinfectants over the still
an article some sense I know in terms of
value whatsoever that the Home Secretary
was instrumental in seeing that not
a word of it appeared in any newspaper but
you never told me anything about this
found you would away at the time I'd
have no intrinsic value or news of such
importance I don't understand they have
a thing with apprehended within fifteen
minutes committing the theft but by that
time it isn't the articles in question that
get to be found before going further Dr
Watson I must inform you that this matter
is not to be mentioned outside of this
room because through an upright amount
of gossip it's not going to that now of
a show in Vegas and have been implied for
years in the position of extreme trust by
the ratings drop into the Bank of England
the articles he stole nothing less than
a complete duplicate set of plates but
printing five pound notes that giving them
down plates possession
and with those plates
a gang of cooks could letting them with
side note not thought she knew just enter
the word but not undertake to boot from
genuine Bank of England notes in any way
whatsoever could have let me put
a toll might have resulted in enormous
damage in taking public confidence in the
trader that tried everything out a
waitress to Davidson offered him
a shorter sentence of
a tell us wait in the late we even
put in Scotland Yard men with him
a cell mates but no results
obviously Davis is
a man of strong character for the patients.
Suddenly feel compelled to smother up
the secret of the hiding place of the plate
is considered right I don't understand
Mr Holmes Well for example that the Bank
of England made any plans to radically
change the design of the five pound note
so that in say seven years from now notes
made from the still in place would be with.
Confidential Mr Holmes that the move
was discussed but we placing all of
five notes in circulation would be such
a Herculean task that nothing's been done
about the days yet I see of course that
as another possible explanation
it doesn't have much time to find
a hiding place before he was captured and
then be afraid that the Fates would be
accidentally discovered before he is
released and his anxiety can mitigate their
whereabouts to this confederates in the
sponsible I believe you to help I'm sure
that the messages contained in this musical
box are rather an opening as you go
boxes since the best of all three themes
to be essential. To thread the but we have
one that oh what do you want to do I'm
trying to use the message from the one that
we have.
The tune is the one played by him or
is music about. Getting different
sounds the same to me
the tune. From how the.
Key to the mystery it must be the fuel. And
the why is why he was doing music about
his to convey the message why
not product is I sure Buffett.
If you inspect. That top in speaking.
Well. Golders Green station reports that
just from tartan Thompson's body and the
time outs on his clothes he was time to run
out of that tactic what an unfortunate
accident not an accident at
hello I'm afraid it's made it.
And you know love to. Many men.
Any. Negative but no disparity
you're going to make.
In your. Entire.
Day will be complete. Or
you're going to meet. No
example many. Babies
appearing. Gentleman by.
Now we. Need things like
a. Baby name with
a little. To the south and this
could around every practice act.
Basketball by seeing the thousand actors
join tend to queue. Waiting outside.
The. Area.
Yet. Again. And.
Yes. You have.
A narrow area and
a. Blimey. All right Joe Now the back
and and I'm thank you I want you to be
dependent on Dr Watson. Anything to
find my hero he gave me
a good ten months that I'll never get as I
do have the most unpleasant charge made
in the last. Five proving to the sentence
that the police the people at the time
blowing up someone safe that's why I
get in. The door now you can help me.
Come up here Saturday and again on
the peace and quiet around the.
Old. Me down now I can
have some peace and quiet
a man Thank you Joe. Five tons of this for
you. I wouldn't want to take it on the
sales but I get somebody to do it for you
for after that the job is yes five damn.
Well that's. Just a sick I want you
to identify a song for me father and
a song has been written that I don't know
that's right and you. Across the violin
is more my instrument. Oh well
here we go now listen to this.
Wait a minute you're playing that
right that should be a natural not
a flat you know the song well yes it's not
a last plane is found. This white man but
your point I don't want that's what I
hoped you'd say that it's not going to go.
At the same tomorrow right but you're
making different mistakes but you did the
first by not mistake joke
on a variation Yeah there's
a song for me with other words written.
OK Joe Well just me know if
you want to something that. I
don't know yet it's probably
a code of some sort Joe if you
will write the song down for me
when it was originally written
down but attack I feel then it.
Pale I want to make fun of it.
Well obviously there's no lyrics no combination
of those words that is of still the
day in the way images Musical Box basic to
the difference in the variations than we
have sure quite yet at the top want to
memorize this tune is played by Emily's box
that night we were limited to that he was
amazing and imagine my definition one of
the first principles in solving crime is
never to disregard anything no matter how
trivial by the three boxes I don't run
because the message was obviously too long
to be conveyed by any one variation and the
third box the one that woman took from
the killer god that contains yet another
set of any actions this is all the army
now all we have to do now is to find
the secret to the variations of
a easy problem to sell it but if.
We have that company.
Which is up right. After this
is coming your way all right.
We have got the one thing common sense.
To me Mr Holmes what happened who called
by the RAF This is Hudson just the only
one who said you wanted to be nice little
gentleman happened again once today and
well be on they didn't like although I
couldn't see if the shadows are heavy black
the feeling that she had such
a nice really well. Some sort of Mr
Holmes it had been anything at all
but you did see I should always like trying
to come in and wait for you about it is
and then why the U.S.
No way of that I think it's quite all right
quite all right I don't what it was it
had been. What wellness
a musical box they didn't get
it get it where is it in your
hand. Now this good job
like this gets off the
top. But your hand inside and
you'll find the music box.
Well down the hole. Using.
Who I suppose smell
a pub of closing time. On
its morning Lama to congratulate you on
a brilliant deduction. Not
transposition on a
polygraph transposition of
a pint glass or any non form of
decoding about the last. Yazid
about three o'clock this morning
when I was only trying to help.
Not again because I was
sometimes wake all night.
Not of the distinguished composition I grant
you that well I don't know one to the
other but I was
a kid my people tried to have it taught
the piano. So if I don't teach it my poor
old girl finally reached
a point of not going to the Keys for me
to sleep even then I never progressed
beyond numbering the keys want to nineteen
the keyboard is the nineteenth letter of
the alphabet. That's all
but note my guess first now the eight T.
Is eight then. The twelve.
L. Sixty F.
. Shall. Piano
lessons or not and then Oh if you
have solved it thank you. Thanks so.
Now I have two thirds of
the. Books. Secretary.
Presumably. These are the first and second
portions of the message and this gang
has the first and third parts
of it precisely and it's
a stalemate. You can't leave it like that
there's no doubt in my mind that they are
trying to secure the message that's missing
and soon you've taken every precaution
to guard the different music classes carefully
hidden the biggest race of Dr Watson
on God However I'm reasonably certain that
difficult as it may be we can find the
plate even without the missing part
of the message that. The secretary
talked to. That side of the fact that
Davidson to get the Bank of England plate
some of the London the stuff I don't see
that leap with Vista told me to point out
to his. P. Words Dr S.
It looks as if the plates were hidden in
the house of the Dr where there stands for
his first or last initial remains to be
determined by process of elimination for
the must be ten thousand
doctors in London with us for
a first or last initial Besides it and every
one of them will have to be questioned
in person that's why I said this
is a task for Scotland Yard it's
a task all right but Scotland Yard
has searched worst case Texas found
a needle well that I'm being. I'll leave
the matter in your hands gentlemen we're
call you if and when we get
a lead on our mysterious stopped us.
Meantime I'm going to follow up
a little too concerning
a cigarette. Certain
of the identification of the tobacco
Absolutely I have made despite your brain for
only three times. It is only
a few what Egyptian without mixture of lack
of but I did not it just didn't show up
pretty near me for sport is one thing
but I do see yes yes and the three
customers. Nature we live in Bombay
India. This is Catherine Leamington
Smith and yes I'm the third and this
is here that Courtney of park mentions
Bryanston Square thank you thank you
very much you've been most helpful is
a pleasure to have been
a service Mr Holmes. Yes
this is
a cocktail Yes and I know Michel icons
do come in thank you. I've heard
of you of course Mr Holland. I believe
we have a mutual friend and so as
a cocktail he spoke to me
of you quite often need.
And to what good fortune of my indebted
for this visit I think your knowledge has
gotten
a lot I did get some in seceding last week
but outside of that I don't think I'm of
any interest to the police how come nobody
has got it you seem to forget that you
and I have met before and thought it I'm
sure I would have remembered meeting the
great geological to sit down thank
your. Stay with us the formal Yes'
at the home of Mr and Mrs
Kilgour one forty three B.
Empty road kill girl. I don't think
I know anyone of that name why
did you say you them so matter back to
called on them when they were out. There and
understand that their home really here
but restaurant differently indeed
cigarette Thank you.
Thank you and I was just
got people generally get
you know screaming in disguise but the
shape of the IS YOUR MOST infallible means
of recognition and identification to the
trained eye and identity of the stake in
this is someone else or not I was told
though naturally I expected your denial.
That when you pay job
visit to my room to make
a street you can either say left
behind another identification. That I.
Identical out there as I
must admit they are is
a motorhome to catch one's
clever is you I have to use
a very special. I knew he had been able
to resist the bait of my cigarette having
read with great interest your monograph on
the ashes of one hundred forty different
varieties of tobacco I should
advise you not to move Mr Holmes
I was congratulate you on your
ingenuity Mrs Courtenay it was indeed
a brilliantly designed trap thank you
with the praise for my master is indeed
gratifying I should always cherish the
memory of your flattering. Memory
precisely in the phrase these gentlemen
of the most regrettable task to perform
unless of course you care to turn over
the missing news Go Bucks with the old
pledge to take no action against us
in the future I'm afraid that will be
impossible I thought that would be
around honeyed test out careful is no
need to be unnecessarily rough with our
distinguished guests you realize that the
harm is that your demise better not take
place the. Coppers that you know well
naturally it shall we go.
So seriously awkward having
a dead body lying about don't you agree
Mr Holmes another dead body way too heavy
on your conscience got it.
Right I have
a cigarette. Don't you I love. The
tadpole Jaimie. It's the breaks I bind.
Thank you about Governor
very considerate of you.
Will make happy to know Mr
Holmes that your death will be
a perilous one. I made. A
touch this to the Metro the
text. That little
attachment I demister comes
contains the dead if you feel it now
no it's not no suffering German purity
progressive find this out
to move in that and.
Stop another.
Papers match.
Up with him I meet.
You find yourself like my hammock
cock. Suspended between heaven.
And to your pillow in the tank. Good it
would be too bad to happen in go round trip
so simple an opus.
Good afternoon Mr shallow Coleman and
I'm Dr Watson was Dr Watson How stupid
of me. To hear me. When you come
in well I really came to see Mr
Holmes while I'm fraid he's out I don't
know what he'll be back that says something
I can do to sit down Thank you you know
a job comes and I've been engaged on it on
a great many cases. The matter of fact to
this very moment when involved in one of
the most baffling of what you tell me all
traveller I have been to help feel very
kind of you Dr Watson Perhaps if I
wouldn't be imposing too much posing
a. Position to talk
a pleasure I show you now tell me all
about this William. I didn't tell
a doctor once and I've come to London sheer
desperation my only sister disappeared
in the local police under the UN able to
find homes and I shot the carriage exactly
like that once very interesting as far as
I remember I call it the invention of the
solitary cyclist. Come to think
we did most of it is similar to
a lot of different. Things.
We're well she's only seventeen
Dr Watson and if you disappeared last
Thursday she seemed to be in the best the
spirit. Possibly for men to can tell me oh
no no nothing of the thought she left no
note didn't even pack
a bag no explanation she just started to
walk to the village from our house in
broad daylight to feed Bannister in
the face of the bulls. Might I have
a glass of water. I want to.
Thank you Dr. And I do not cry anymore it
was pull yourself together in much better
already knowing that you're going
to help me not to want to put him.
To give you the plug then. Having to
fire extinguisher. Like
we have the instinct.
To Once we will have this
thing out of the car.
Just to make. You say there was.
No need for the target uproar.
I hope you weren't too
frightened or swims. Gone
to trial balloon they always lose
their heads in the mood to who.
Do. New school.
Great Scott. Ms Williams.
Well. Good and Helen by now Mr Hope
there's no doubt exchanged his
violin for the. Always
assuming that Heaven is
a destination. Not that we have
a missing musical box. Nineteen
now we can. Thank you letter.
You sit home is where we will be I'll be
trying to get you to come out Scotland
Yard all over London. Looking
probably in the wrong places I was
a terrible things happen I've
been duped that woman he met
a complete fool but I want to meet Well
she came here that also spoke about I
thought the whole place on fire my first
thought was to say the musical box on it
sent it all to has box does not
let me sell too much of it.
Is next in the cover
antagonist. Snowpack is it.
Where you can going to sell yourself with
the thought that your charming friend is
at least
a reader of the US but you may if I remember
correctly you wrote about my little
experiment to smoke in the client saga story
entitled A scandal in Bohemia but just
disappeared in the Strand
magazine All right all right
a boy who rub it in. That Major
you have to know that you made
a fool of me till. That cigarette stop
the planet you ever want to express
Tempest. Going to better Ging around the
space than if you want to not have that
explanations I have to wait until late at
the moment for the problem which I feel
is insurmountable come over here right.
Out of permanence and possession of all
three parts of the code here are we able
the Bank of England plates. Into their
possession chapel for the tune up Dr Samuel
Johnson once said There is no problem
in the mind of man can set the mind of man
cannot saw but that over and it is good
enough to say no Johnson he said
there is no Watson thank you I'm
leaving the front reception room we come
into the main hall where Dr Johnson was in
the habit of passing through to have his
meager meals in the dining allowed to sit
in company with his friend
and biographer James
a possible. We will never pass up the
Stelly which remains in its natural would
finish just as it was when the good doctor
was here the framed edging on the wall
is believed to have been presented to Dr
Johnson by the distinguished painter so
Joshua Reynolds.
Thompson is that important
my dear. Or I'm sorry. This
way they just didn't want to use the
sleep number until then moving on. The
secretary not on this last patient Tammy
I have no idea let's hear what comes out
of the way of what could go wrong.
And here we have the Gallup library in which
Dr Johnson wrote his famous dictionary
and which you will see also many of the
great man's books and other items of
interest step forward
a dozen done by the simple standing in the
corner is the secretary which contains
many of the original works by the literary
genius on his table Dr Johnson's catch
clouds used to sleep
while his master learned
a strange thing about this country to suggest
them was his lovable asked us they do
say that the deduct often went hungry to
find the cat that delicacy. What is good
is. Now we will visit the grain room which
is immediately below us in which you
will see the very bade in which Dr
Johnson died but didn't guy. Gal out
just out. This way ladies and
gents was my understand streets.
To keep.
Shells up.
And I. Can't
remember the Bank of England
played. Well it cost. Me to get.
So I couldn't do that if I were you going
to come out. And that's congratulate you
Mr Holmes Thus far more clever
than I. Thank you Mrs got me.
Praise from you did gratifying. I've always
cherish the memory of your flattering
word memory. Thank you and now I have
a most regrettable task to part.
Oh. I hope. You're right that the
giving you also but I think the
sentiment on the float across the middle
attention we will see that it looks is
best to nobody's hanged
take him in charge. It's.
A. Brilliant antagonist
it's
a visit how tense for some is directed
when you see that the states return to the
Bank of England inspector I still don't
understand how you saw this I was in town
to go to Dr Watson he gave me the drill
but he mentioned Dr Samuel Johnson
congratulations Dr thank you so much I don't
think I'd have done the job that other
sounds help you know.